cityvoter.com 2019-10-29

# CityVoter :: Privacy Policy

* * *

##### The effective date of this Agreement is May 1, 2015.

CityVoter, Inc. (”CityVoter”) is an online and mobile platform that helps people find products and services and tell consumers which businesses are the most popular based on annual contests. Part of our service includes soliciting and aggregating votes and user recommendations. Our users vote, share their favorites, create lists, ask questions, invite friends, and write recommendations about local businesses. These recommendations are posted on our web site, mobile application, and web sites we create with sponsor partner (collectively the ”Platform”). We also interact with marketing partners to bring to the attention of our users products and services we believe the users will find interesting (sponsor partners and marketing partners are collectively referred to as the ”Partners”). We also engage with Merchants (the ”Merchants”) to make available discounted products and services to users on behalf of the Merchants. This privacy policy (”Privacy Policy”) outlines the types of personal information we may collect when you use the CityVoter service (”Service”), which is further described in the Terms of Service (”Terms and Conditions”) available at https://cityvoter.com/help/terms-and-conditions as well as some of the steps we take to secure it. 

Voting results and recommendations can be accessed and read by other CityVoter users. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, a ”user” is defined as someone using the CityVoter Platform, and a ”friend” is defined as someone you have explicitly invited to share questions or local information with you. 

By using CityVoter, you permit the collection and use of your personal information as outlined below. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. 

##### 1\. Information We Collect

CityVoter collects user submitted personally identifiable information through the account registration process; such as full name, email address, gender, year of birth and location information including city, state or zip code to identify you and send you notifications related to the use of the Service. CityVoter also collects user submitted photos, reviews, and ratings of local businesses. If you purchase a Deal Voucher (as defined in the Terms and Conditions) we refer you to a third-party Payment Vendor (as defined in the Terms and Conditions) who will collect your credit card information to complete the transaction. 

Some information collected is non-personally identifiable information, such as; your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, timestamp, and the subject of advertisements you may have clicked on or scrolled over. 

##### 2\. How We Use Your Information

Information such as your screen name, profile photo and any personally identifiable information you have included in your questions or comments may be shown to friends or other users primarily in conjunction with Services of the CityVoter Platform. In addition, we may syndicate your questions or voting results from your questions to third parties, in which case your screen name and any personally identifiable information you have included in your questions or recommendations may be shown to users of such third party web sites. 

We share and/or license your information with both our Partners and Merchants. As a user of the Service you acknowledge and agree that CityVoter shall have the right to share and/or license your information with its Partners and Merchants and, in the event that you purchase a Deal Voucher, with our pre-approved Payment Vendors. 

We may also use your email address to send you newsletters, contest promotions, special offers and updates regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by managing the subscriptions associated with your profile. Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message). Our Partners may also send you emails with offers or information believed pertinent to you, but you may choose not to receive these emails in accordance with the Partner's opt-out process. 

We and our Partners collect non personally identifiable information such as hashed data, click stream information, browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, timestamp data and the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over. Such information help us diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the CityVoter Service, in order to provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Platform and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on, their advertisements. Partners may utilize cookies, pixels, or other technologies to collect and use the non-personally identifiable information during your visits to ours and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info and Networking Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. 

##### 3\. Transfer of Information

We share and/or license your information with our Partners, Merchants, and Payment Vendors and may transfer your information to these parties during the course of providing the Service or for marketing campaigns. We also may syndicate your questions, lists or voting results from your contests to third parties, in which case your screen name and any personally identifiable information you have included in your questions, lists or recommendations may be shown to users of such third party web sites. 

CityVoter will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, CityVoter may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of CityVoter, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, the personal information about you is transferred and may become subject to a different privacy policy. 

CityVoter will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

##### 4\. Use of Cookies

Like most websites, CityVoter requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small text files that reside on a user’s computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time. You should be aware that CityVoter cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or any information advertisers may gather from their use of cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the CityVoter Platform. 

##### 5\. Controlling Your Personal Information

As a registered CityVoter user, you can modify your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing the ”Settings” section of the site. If you wish to have your information removed or your account terminated, you can contact CityVoter support@cityvoter.com. CityVoter will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your personal information from the Platform. As with most websites, it may be impossible to remove your account and comments without some residual information being retained by CityVoter. 

##### 6\. Security

Your CityVoter account is password-protected. We use industry standard measures to protect your information that is stored within our database. We limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact privacy@cityvoter.com. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

_You hereby acknowledge that CityVoter is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet or via mobile carriers, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner._

##### 7\. Children

The CityVoter website is not directed to children. CityVoter does not knowingly solicit information from any child under the age of 13. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or a parent or guardian) to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information. 

##### 8\. Third Party Links and Advertising

Our website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. CityVoter does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy polices on these third party websites. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Platform. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

##### 9\. Notice of Privacy to California Residents

Under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the ”Act”), we are required to inform users of our Platform who reside in the state of California what information we have collected from you and information as to how to update or change that information. To receive this information, please send us a letter in writing at CityVoter, 300 Seminary Ave #281, Manchester Vt, 05254. The letter should include what Personally Identifiable Information you would like updated or removed. Your letter must contain your name, address, and email address. 

##### 10\. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Statement

By using the Platform, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Platform. CityVoter may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy and/or the way we use our users’ personally identifiable information, then we will post a prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Policy and also on our home page. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at privacy@cityvoter.com or 

  * CityVoter, Inc.
  * 300 Seminary Ave #281
  * Manchester Vt, 05254
